Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mohammed-ameer-05245a60 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Machine Learning
Internet of Things (IoT)
Electronics

Certifications

Python for Beginners

Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence
Deep Learning

The Python Programmer Bootcamp

IOT using NodeMCU(Powered by ESP8266), MicroPython & PyCharm

Mohammed Ameer

Freelance Trainer - Deep Learning, Machine Learning and IoT Bengaluru

Summary

I am a skilled trainer for Deep Learning, Neural Networks and Internet of Things. I am an innovative training professional with experience in teaching and training, working on mostly on Robotics and IoT Projects for many leading educational training companies all over India. I am an expert in the field of AI,ML, IoT and deliver workshops and seminars on the same for the school and college going students. I have delivered more than 100 workshops all over India. I have trained more than 4000 students on various technical subjects.

I am also the founder of Diazonic Labs, Bengaluru an online edutech company which delivers workshops and webinars on various upcoming technologies ranging from Robotics to Machine Learning. I have pursued Bachelors of Engineering degree in Electronics and communication.

I am very active in guiding robotic enthusiasts for various robotics projects and competitions.

I am also a Robotic consultant for Times of India NIE program and Edu4sure company. My aim is to bring out the talent in youth by unveiling them the latest technology.

My YouTube channel: http://www.youtube.com/diazoniclabs

Experience

Diazonic Labs

Deep Learning, Machine Learning and IoT trainer

September 2016 - Present (4 years)

Bangalore

Edu4Sure

Team Lead Trainer for Python 2018 - Present (2 years)

Freelance Python trainer

QtPi Robotics Robotics Trainer February 2017 - February 2018 (1 year 1 month) Bangalore

Fracktal Works
PCB Designer
November 2016 - January 2017 (3 months)
Bangalore

Education

REVA University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2012 - 2016)

The Regency Public School - India (2007 - 2010)